Ki A Kar Do
Jai Ho Om Maa
Kar Do That
before starting the video today I would
like to thank all of you very much for the way you liked our last video so much.
Thank you for your
comments, questions page, thank you for
supporting. If you will support us like this,
I am your help consultant, Kaju. So
let's start the video. In today's
video, we will learn about Bajaj Finance Company's
health insurance plan, Health In Free
Plan. First of all, we will learn
about the highlights of these plans, that is, what
special features you get in the health
benefit plan.
So the first and best feature of Islam is
that in this plan, you do
not face any limit on the benefit. Secondly, you
can choose a health insurance policy for yourself according to the room rent.
You get infection treatment cover
on which you will not have any kind of penalty in Islam.
Priyanka
is covered for Hathras Junction. Road ambulance charges are covered for you.
See, treatment is covered for you.
You also get the facility of help worker. You can take Islam
individually for yourself, children and  You
can also take it with patience.
People below 45 years of age do not need to undergo
any kind of free medical health
checkup to take this plan.
After a waiting period of 36 months, you
can discover pre-existing insurance in this plan and
you get income tax benefits.
So this is about the
highlights of this plan. Now
we will know about the validity period and benefits of this plan. If we
talk about
age, that is, people of which age
can take this plan.
In Airtel School, the age limit has been defined from 18 years to 65 years
and in this plan, the child insurance limit has been
defined from 3 months to 25 years.
Talking about premium, you get renewal in this plan for
life time. The first
term i.e. the policy period is 3 years and
you can also add the premium of the policy in yearly, half yearly,
water policy and Mandi Board.
This plan is available to you on both Hindi and family
floater basis. If you
want this plan, then  About the coverage, first of all
you get the
benefit of Hospitalization Express coverage in which the room rent expenses are
given to you according to the code a room and tricks you have gifted your plan, your
details of how many room rent options are available to you in Islam are
coming at your speed, you get the information of the expenses of suggestion to Priyanka in
which the previous position is covered
for seven days and post week addition is
covered for 90 days, roadways you
are covered for maximum ₹5000, apart from these there
is top Islamic cover in the policy institute,
now we will talk about the benefits of this plan,
friends, you get the benefit of free health check-up
on Islam, if you remain
associated with this policy for 3 years,
you get this benefit of maximum ₹5000,
you can also reduce your waiting period in this plan,
if you remain covered in Islam
without any break,
you are able to avail some discount like
Five West's Velvet in this account  You
also get a family discount of 5 per cent, subject to certain limits, which is
given to two eligible family
members. You also get a long-term policy discount,
which you get for
purchasing if your policy term is 2 years
and eight per cent if your policy term is 3 years.
You get an employee discount of 20 per
cent if you are an employee of Bajaj Finance Company.
You are charged some amount for room rent
in Spain, the
details of which are appearing on your screen. If you add
this line about the waiting period,
then it shows a waiting period of 30 months.
For specific diseases, you have a waiting period of 24 months.
For West Indies, you have a waiting period of 36 months.
Apart from this, you
get a free look period of 15 days. You
also get the cancellation facility on this.
You get tax benefits
under section 80G. Friends, this was a little
information about the health insurance plan of Bajaj Allianz Company.
Please tell me through comments
how you liked this video about insurance plans. If you have any
doubt or question related to this video,
then ask me through comments.
If you found this video really useful, then
go to WhatsApp and share this video
with your relatives.
What will happen through this is that it will help them and you will get
thanks. So do
not forget to subscribe to my channel and
like the video so that my
motivation remains the same and I will keep bringing
such domestic videos for you.
Press the bell icon so that
you get the latest update regarding the videos
first. Thank you for watching our video
[Music]